<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-08-30T21:44:31-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Stuff Like That There</title><subtitle>A random smattering of scintillating things.  It could be tech, it could be books, it could be theology.  It also could be cat pictures.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Wat?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/stuff/2019/08/30/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wat?" /><published>2019-08-30T21:26:29-04:00</published><updated>2019-08-30T21:26:29-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stuff/2019/08/30/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/stuff/2019/08/30/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;I have not blogged on the internet in a very long time.  This has been a pretty good thing, mostly, but I’m finding that in some cases, I’m not interacting with my reading or my work in the same way because I’m not writing as much.  While I would prefer to scribble in my notebook, the fact of the matter is that I spend 8+ hours a day on a computer, and it would probably be easier to jot down thoughts on things in this format.  It may also allow friends or strangers to interact with it as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a bit of Yo La Tengo theme to the site, but that’s only because their album titles are so witty.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I have not blogged on the internet in a very long time. This has been a pretty good thing, mostly, but I’m finding that in some cases, I’m not interacting with my reading or my work in the same way because I’m not writing as much. While I would prefer to scribble in my notebook, the fact of the matter is that I spend 8+ hours a day on a computer, and it would probably be easier to jot down thoughts on things in this format. It may also allow friends or strangers to interact with it as well.</summary></entry></feed>